Poland
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Poland
2.1.1.1.23
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1237
- Poland, 2.1.1.1.23
  - Polish man and boy, Warsaw, 1913; 25; 2427; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Child crying, Warsaw, 1913; 26; 2428; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Exterior of shop, Warsaw, 1913; 27; 2429; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Two children, Warsaw, 1913; 28; 2430; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Man and woman, Warsaw, 1913; 29; 2431; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Funeral, Warsaw, 1913; 30; 2432; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Jewish people on the street, Warsaw, 1913; 31; 2433; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - People in street, Warsaw, 1913; 32; 2434; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Polish people in street, Warsaw, 1913; 33; 2435; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Old Jewish man, Warsaw, 1913; 34; 2436; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Street scene, people, Warsaw, 1913; 35; 2437; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Sleeping cab driver, Warsaw, 1913; 36; 2438; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Man carrying load, Warsaw, 1913; 37; 2439; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Woman and child, Warsaw, 1913; 38; 2440; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Group of Jewish people, Warsaw, 1913; 39; 2441; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Jewish man, Warsaw, 1913; 40; 2442; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - A wagon load, Warsaw, 1913; 41; 2443; 4x5 (Box 1237)
  - Church of the Holy Cross where Chopin’s heart is buried, Warsaw, 1913; 42; 2444; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Frank R. Roberson at the Statue of Sobieski, Warsaw, 1913; 43; 2445; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Greek cathedral, Warsaw, 1913; 44; 2446; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Saint Florian Church, Praga, Warsaw, 1913; 45; 2447; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Path in Lazienki Park, Warsaw, 1913; 46; 2448; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Greek church and park, Warsaw, 1913; 47; 2449; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Flower boxes, Warsaw, 1913; 48; 2450; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Church of the Holy Cross where Chopin’s heart is buried, Warsaw, 1913; 49; 2451; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Lazienki Palace from distance, Warsaw, 1913; 50; 2452; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  - Saint Florian Church and Praga from Warsaw, 1913; 51; 2453; 5x7 (Box 1237)
  Box 1238
- Poland, 2.1.1.1.23
  - University, Warsaw, 1913; 1; 2454; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - University, Warsaw, 1913; 2; 2455; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Church of Alexander, Warsaw, 1913; 3; 2456; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Fine store, Warsaw, 1913; 4; 2457; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - City hall and police office, Warsaw, 1913; 5; 2458; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Roses, Lazienki Park, Warsaw, 1913; 6; 2459; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Church of the Virgin Mary, Warsaw, 1913; 7; 2460; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Chief Russian Greek church for military in Warsaw, 1913; 8; 2461; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Market square, Warsaw, 1913; 9; 2462; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Fountain in market square, Warsaw, 1913; 10; 2463; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - On the Warsaw side of the Vistula, 1913; 11; 2464; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - The bridge across the Vistula, Warsaw, 1913; 12; 2465; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Russian engine at Villanov, near Warsaw, 1913; 13; 2466; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Mickiewiczowi statue, Warsaw, 1913; 14; 2467; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Corner of Marszalkowska and Bagatela streets, Warsaw, 1913; 15; 2468; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Business street, Warsaw, 1913; 16; 2469; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Street in Warsaw, 1913; 17; 2470; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Street scene, Warsaw, 1913; 18; 2471; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Jewish quarter, Warsaw, 1913; 19; 2472; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Street in Jewish quarter, Warsaw, 1913; 20; 2473; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Flower boxes on residence, Warsaw, 1913; 21; 2474; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - In the Jewish quarter, Warsaw, 1913; 22; 2475; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Lazienki Park, Warsaw, 1913; 23; 2476; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Saxon Garden, Warsaw, 1913; 24; 2477; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Sigismund II column, Warsaw, 1913; 25; 2478; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Toward Sigismund Square from Bristol Hotel, Warsaw, 1913; 26; 2479; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Home of General Scallon, Lazienki Park, Warsaw, 1913; 27; 2480; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - New apartments, Warsaw, 1913; 28; 2481; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Copernicus monument, Warsaw, 1913; 29; 2482; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Residence of attorney, Warsaw, 1913; 30; 2483; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Fine residence, Warsaw, 1913; 31; 2484; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Flower beds, Saxon Gardens, Warsaw, 1913; 32; 2485; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Private house, Warsaw, 1913; 33; 2486; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Street in Warsaw, 1913; 34; 2487; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Church in which Sobieski’s heart is buried, Warsaw, 1913; 35; 2488; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Entrance to Lazienki Park, Warsaw, 1913; 36; 2489; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Lazienki Palace, home of Stanislas Augustus Poniatowski, Warsaw, 1913; 37; 2490; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Main boulevard in Warsaw, Hotel Bristol in distance on right, owned by Paderviski, 1913; 38; 2491; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Main Jewish business street in Warsaw, 1913; 39; 2492; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - General Sobieski’s monument at Lazienki Park, Warsaw, 1913; 40; 2493; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Polytechnique, Warsaw, 1913; 41; 2494; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Synagogue in Warsaw, 1913; 42; 2495; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Grand opera house, Warsaw, 1913; 43; 2496; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Palace Villanov, Warsaw, 1913; 44; 2497; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Chief Russian Greek church, Warsaw, 1913; 45; 2498; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Art museum, Warsaw, 1913; 46; 2499; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Park in palace grounds at Villanov, Warsaw, 1913; 47; 2500; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Tree avenue at Villanov, Warsaw, 1913; 48; 2501; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  - Family tomb of Villanov noble family, Warsaw, 1913; 49; 2502; 5x7 (Box 1238)
  Box 1239
- Poland, 2.1.1.1.23
  - Church at Villanov, Warsaw, 1913; 1; 2503; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Mr. Horodinsky at Villanov, Warsaw, 1913; 2; 2504; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Henryk Sienkiewicz, copy, before 1914; 3; 27X; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Raoul Koczalski, copy, before 1914; 4; 30X; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Starzec, copy, before 1914; 5; 37X; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Lubelskie, copy, before 1914; 6; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Pow Sieradzki, copy, before 1914; 7; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Huculka, copy, before 1914; 8; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Hucul, copy, before 1914; 9; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Pow Zamoyski, copy, before 1914; 10; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Morskie Oko, copy, before 1914; 11; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Czarny staw pod Koscielcem, copy, before 1914; 12; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Widok z Koziego Wierchu, copy, before 1914; 13; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Staw Smereczynski, copy, before 1914; 14; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Wodospad Mickiewicza, copy, before 1914; 15; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Siklawa, copy, before 1914; 16; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Wysoka, copy, before 1914; 17; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Turnia Popradzka, copy, before 1914; 18; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Siklawica w Strazyskach, copy, before 1914; 19; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Skala sowy w dol Koscieliskiej, copy, before 1914; 20; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Kominy w Strazyskach, copy, before 1914; 21; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Dolina Bialego, copy, before 1914; 22; 4x5 (Box 1239)